

Duvan José Baena

Medellín, Colombia Carrera 21 Nro. 59 -34 (+57) 3122988419

Id profesional 05255-351402

<u>djbpuerta@hotmail.com</u> <u>https://duvanbaena.com</u>

Skills

Agile Methodologies Working Together Lifelong learning

Certification (6)

Microsoft Certified: Azure Solutions Architect Expert

Microsoft Certified: DevOps

Engineer Expert

Microsoft Certified: Azure Administrator Associate

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform App Maker Associate

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Fundamentals

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals

About me

I am an English language and literature student; I love read and music, I like software development. I am an open-source believer and a faithful follower of DevOps. I have knowledge and experience in the public cloud Azure and Azure DevOps platform and power platform (office 365). I am also well informed about the definition of IAC, about the use of methods to release applications to customers through automation CI/CD multi-platform.

Finally, I have knowledge some tasks of SysAdmin (write shell scripts, document everything, check component on-premises and basic handling of Linux.

Experience

DevOps & Cloud Engineer - Globo Studio of Colombia S.A.S, (2018 – 2021) Present

Administration within the Azure ecosystem, complemented using CI/CD technologies and management of source code repositories.

Monitoring the availability of Cloud PaaS/SaaS solutions, performance, and production of health systems in support of meeting service level objectives.

IT Infrastructure Engineer - Colombia National Police 2008 - 2018

Research, advise, and implement the best practices to maintain the infrastructure.

Maximizing network efficiency by monitoring performance, troubleshooting network problems and outages, scheduling upgrades.

Education

University of Medellin, Col (2019 - 2020)

Software Engineering Specialist

CESDE, Col (2015 - 2018)

Computer Software Technician

Universidad Católica Luis Amigó, Col (2011 - 2017)

Systems Engineering Degree